ILR School Alumni Memorabilia /4118 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Alumni Memorabilia
1958-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4118 MB
4.28 cubic feet
4.4 linear ft.
Memorabilia.
This collection consists of memorabilia from alumni of the ILR School.
8247818
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 16, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 17, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4078: ILR School 40th Anniversary Documents /4119m: ILR School Richard Jacobstein Memorabilia /4120: ILR School Alumni Scrapbooks
Layzer, Judith; Cook, Alice Hanson; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations -- Archives; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations -- Collectivles
8247818
- Alice Cook's Passport (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Memories in Celebration of the Life of Alice Hanson Cook (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  2 copies
- Alice Don't Go! - (hand made card for Alice Cook) (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Baptism Certificate for Alice Cook (Box 2, Folder 4)
- A Reception celebrating the Opening of the Rose K. Goldsen Papers with remarks by Alice H. Cook photographs (Box 2, Folder 5)
  11 photographs, both color and black and white, newspaper clippings
- Miscellaneous Photos and articles (Box 2, Folder 6)
  3 photos
- Older Passport photo and paperwork for Alice Cook (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Picture of Alice Cook as an infant (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Photo copies of Alice Cook photos (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Infant photograph of Alice Hanson Cook (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Photo of Alice Cook and some of the other faculty members from ILR (Box 2, Folder 11)
- From Judith Layzer - 1958 Class notes (Box 2, Folder 12)
  photo copy
- Cornell Letter Openers, engraved with Cornell University ILR School, Celebration 2007 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  2 pieces
- Red T-Shirt 'Labor Works' (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Black T-Shirt - May Day '80 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Congratulations Alice card, hand made and signed (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Alice Cook's Grammar school diploma, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Recognition of Alice Cook's assistance with training of new employees at the Institut Fur Arbeiterbildung Berlin (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Alice Preston Hanson (Cook) Diploma from Northwestern University Easton-Chicago, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Monogrammed briefcase (Box 2, Folder 20)
- School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Building Dedication, April 17, 1998 -- Paper weight (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Oval, looks like green marble
- NYSSILR. Alumni Memorabilia - Alice Cook Diploma (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous photographs and articles about Alice Cook (Box 3, Folder 2)
  3 photographs, news clippings
- Commemorative paper weights - School of Industrial and Labor Relations - Building Dedication, April 17, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)